(SCREAMING)
(JUNGLE-STYLE MUSIC)
(SCREAM)
(RADIO ON - BLARING POP SONG)
(TAP SQUEAKS)
(RADIO MUSIC CONTINUES)
(ALARM BUZZES)
(WHEELS WHIRRING)
(WHIRR OF BIKE WHEELS)
(MECHANISM WHINES)
Ha-ha-ha! Ha-ha!
You missed! You missed this time.
you little menace!
I beat you!
Morning.
- You're getting upset over nothing!
- I'm not.
A nice breakfast will cheer you up.
I'm not getting upset over...
What is that (?)
- It's bacon.
- I know it's bacon.
What have you done to it?
You said you didn't like the grease
from fried bacon. So I boiled it.
(RADIO - POP MUSIC)
What is Lane doing up
at this hour on a Sunday?
Doesn't he turn to dust
if the sun hits him?
It's try-outs for the ski team.
He's going to Mount Brodie with Beth.
Sure. he can't do anything
without that girl.
I tell you. Jenny.
that boy is obsessed.
Now. honey... Obsessed?
Do we not throw empty things away?
Oh.
What in the name
of all that's holy?
Badger likes the prizes you get
from cutting the coupons out.
- He's mailing them today.
- Can't you wait until?
Lane. the closet door can be closed
as well as opened.
Ooh!
- Sorry. Dad.
- Lane. your breakfast is getting cold.
Thanks. I can't have breakfast.
I got trials today.
I don't want to throw up again.
I had to buy that guy a new hat
last time. Bye. Dad.
Lane!
I would like to meet you tonight
to discuss the future of that vehicle.
which you purchased months ago.
yet has darkened our drive ever since.
Noted. Talk to you tonight.
Gotta pick up Beth.
(SIGHS)
Ricky! Ricky!
Ricky! Don't be so shy! Come here.
Monique. this is Ricky.
Ricky. this is Monique. the French
student who'll be staying with us.
(GARGLED SNORT)
Ah!
It's an awesome spectacle.
an audacious display
of seething opponents.
once again. parallel.
in an obstinate attempt
to prove superiority of the roads.
unequalled in our lifetime.
The crowds swell with anticipation
as the lights turn green!
You stupid bonehead! You idiot!
- Sir...
- Get out of this car!
If he asks me. I'll go out with him.
I mean. he skis the K-12.
Yeah. he's so boss!
Lane? I'll tell him after trials. You
know how he gets when he gets upset.
Yeah... from the chairlifts! He had
to buy the guy a new hat last time.
(CAR HORN)
Lane's here. I gotta go.
I'll call you later. Bye.
He's the only person that's skied
the K-12 from the glacier and lived.
Man! What a hunk!
Your time has to be under 58 seconds
to even be considered for the team.
Your time will be gauged along with
a rating of one to ten on your style.
judged solely by me and my vast
expertise of skiing technique.
Why don't you sorry-looking hopefuls
make your way up the hill?
The girls can keep me company
till it's time for you to take the track.
Who'd like to... hold my clipboard?
What's your name?
- Charles De Mar.
- Shut up. geek. What's your name?
- Beth.
- That's my favourite name.
- Roy Stalin. How you doing?
- Lane Myer.
You and I share one common desire.
to be part of the well-oiled machinery
that is Greendale School Ski Team.
The desire for victory!
- Well...
- Let's see what you got!
- Ready up there?
- We're all set.
- What is the next victim's name?
- Myer. Lane Myer.
- Is that as in Oscar Mayer?
- That's a roger.
Beth. you were standing with Oscar.
Is he your main wiener man?
Don't listen to Stalin. kid.
He's a punk. Now you show him.
Show him how a skier really skis.
- We're sending him down.
- Counting down.
Drei. frei. go!
Too bad. Real close. Next.
(BETH) Lane. I think we should talk.
We've been seeing a lot of each other.
It's in my interests to go out
with someone more popular.
better-looking. drives a nicer car.
Six months! Six months.
and she just dumps me for him.
For Stalin. just like that!
Six months!
Truly a sight to behold.
A man. beaten.
The once great champ.
now a study in moppishness.
No longer the victory-hungry stallion
we've raced so many times before.
but a pathetic. washed-up.
aged ex-champion.
All right. let's go!
Someone gonna see God.
I want to break your goddamn neck!
Get out! Get out of the car!
- Hello. Lane. How was your day?
- Beth broke up with me.
- That's nice.
- We're through. That's it.
What the hell? Wait a minute here.
Wait. this is death here.
I haven't even been to New York City.
I haven't been anywhere!
Suicide is never the answer.
little trooper.
Greendale is a small town. Lane.
It's a fly speck on the map
on the way to a ski slope.
I can't even get real drugs here!
Stalin's a hero.
the only one who can ski the K-12.
You're a great skier.
but he's incredible.
If I skied the K-12.
do you think she'd take me back?
Now I'm back to suicide again.
(MOM) We're all going
to enjoy this treat.
I got the recipe from
the "Ladies' Home Journal".
The mail got wet.
so some of the pages ran together.
I improvised
with my own little ideas.
You see. it's got... raisins in it.
You like raisins!
There is still one more thing
I'd like to discuss with Lane.
The subject here...
...is the mystery car...
Thank you.
...which. even as we speak. darkens
our domain under a mouldy tarp.
- You know the car of which I speak?
- Yeah...
Let me refresh your memory.
Cast your mind back.
It's a crisp September morning.
You borrowed $200
to purchase the car.
because your girlfriend Beth
said it was...
I believe the term was "tasty".
Since then. that "tasty" car
has slept in an auto-cocoon
on my front lawn!
I'll get around to it.
Lane. have you seen the student
who's staying at the Smiths' house?
Go over and welcome her to our town.
She'd like that.
Mrs Smith probably got her so that
her weird son could see a real girl!
He never goes outdoors. just sits
in that house and crochets all day.
The Chapmans had their student
for six months.
- He became a son to Jules and Irene.
- That kid from El Salvador?
Can I be excused?
I'm not feeling well.
I'm just gonna be excused.
I can't figure it out. Badger.
You seem smart. Why do you waste
your time with this kid stuff?
You're almost eight.
OK.
Beth... It was love at first sight.
Red Dog. Red Dog! 92! 74! 16! 43!
Bring it home. Momma!
- Hi.
- So. how do you like Greendale?
- Fine.
- You find the school system adequate?
- School hasn't started yet.
She itched her nose. A message to me
that there was something on my nose?
That's funny.
He wiped his nose after I did.
Maybe I got some dirt on my nose.
He's too embarrassed to tell me!
I must look sickening!
There she goes again!
What could it be? Relish on my nose?
How gross! She might think
it's a... Oh. not that. please!
Please don't let it be a booger.
Please. God!
I don't get it.
How could she throw away six months?
I mean. six months. just like that!
No explanation. no reason.
Just... Just throw it away!
How can you throw away six months?
When you're... in love with someone...
Six months! I'm history!
Just like that. I'm gone.
She's probably just testing me.
Big test. That's probably it.
- (DOORBELL)
- That's her. That's her!
- Johnny...
- Four weeks.
Twenty papers.
That's two dollars. plus tip.
I don't have a dime. Sorry.
I didn't ask for a dime! Two dollars!
Well. it's funny.
My mom had to leave early
to take my brother to school.
Two dollars... cash!
The problem is that my little brother
got an arm caught in the microwave.
My grandmother dropped acid
and freaked out
and hijacked a bus full of penguins.
It's kind of a family crisis.
so come back later. Great.
(CAR RADIO: "BREAKING UP
IS HARD TO DO")
# Breaking up is hard to do... #
# Don't take your love... #
# And she's gone... #
# Fifty ways to leave your lover... #
# It hurts so bad... #
# They say that breaking up
is hard to do... #
The three cardinal.
trapezoidal formations.
hereto made orientable
in our diagram
by connecting the various points.
HIGK. PEGQ and LMNO.
creating our geometric
configurations.
which have no properties.
but with location...
(ALL) Aah!
...are equal to the described
triangle CAB quintuplicated.
Therefore...
...the five triangles composing
the aforementioned NIGH
each are equal to the triangle CAB
in this geometric concept!
Therefore. in a like manner.
the geometric metaphors can
derive a repeated vectoral sum.
This was your assignment.
I would like to see the results. please.
Take them out!
Oops.
- Sophia...
- Oh! Oh! Oh!
- Oh. please!
- And... Buster.
- Me! Me! Please!
- And... Beth.
- And...
- Oh. please. please. please!
Mr Myer. Please join us
at the blackboard
and show us your solution
to this paltry geometric dilemma.
- (SCREECH)
- (ALL) Oh...!
Oh. sorry.
Lane. would you relax?!
It's just our virginity!
Oh. I agree. totally.
We should tell someone or do
something or get my Dad's Polaroid.
- What was that?
- What?
I heard something.
You're in the most secluded place in
the northern hemisphere. We're alone.
Come on.
- What's wrong?
- That thing I put on me. it broke.
Broke? It broke?!
- Take it easy. I'll buy a new one.
- I don't want a new one!
I'm sorry!
(BELL)
(ALL) Aw!
Now. now. now.
I'll see you all tomorrow.
Remember to memorise pages
39 to 110 for tomorrow's lesson.
- (ALL) All right!
- Cool!
(GIRL) Mr Kerber
really just makes geometry live.
Lane. listen. I've been thinking
about what you told me last night.
- I've decided I'm going to help you.
- How?
I've been going to this high school
for seven and a half years.
I'm no dummy.
I know high-school girls.
Two things. One. how about your sax?
- I mean. Roy plays the guitar.
- He does?
Yeah. You know. girls love that.
Why don't you take up your sax again?
- Number two?
- The K-12. dude.
You make a gnarly run like that
and girls will get sterile
just looking at you.
Mr Myer. would you stay behind?
I'd like a word with you.
- We'll do this.
- Talk to you later.
- Lane...
- Yes. sir?
- This is a bit awkward.
- Yes. sir.
Well... I've heard a few things and...
Well. I was wondering...
...if you would mind if I took out Beth.
(SLURPING)
(RO Y) # And I love you so much
# 'Cause I met you in first grade... #
(GROWLS)
What did you go and do that for?
Really. Lane. why? That's sick.
Sick? Beth. I love you.
How could you dump me for him?
Face it. Lane. You're a no-show.
a loss. You're immature.
You can't do a thing by yourself.
You're a spastic nerve bag.
Besides. Roy can ski the K- 12.
How could I enjoy myself
with you as a boyfriend?
Any girl would be overwhelmed
to go out with me.
Chris Cummins? You haven't a chance.
- She'd go out with me in a second.
- Listen.
Chris dates the basketball team.
Not certain members. the whole team!
Talk to her and you're dead.
- So just give it up.
- Yeah. Oscar Mayer. A fine idea.
I will not give it up. Beth!
Some day you'll want me back!
Sorry.
I'm gonna get some milk.
Just one milk. I'll be OK!
Watch this.
- Can I borrow these?
- What's the big idea?
Buy yourself another leotard.
I'll be back in a minute.
Excuse me.
(GROUP GRUNT)
I was thinking...
You skate. I skate. we skate.
Maybe we could get together...
- You're a jerk.
...and be a skating team.
- (BELL)
- Chris. all I was saying was really...
See you later. guys!
(SHRIEKS)
(GRUNTS AND GROWLS)
- Lane!
- What?
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
Yes. you are.
Buck up. little camper!
We'll beat that slope together.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I'm right behind you. buddy!
Ah-aah-aa...
Man. that's a real shame
when folks be throwing away
a perfectly good white boy!
If I could get past this first lift.
the rest would be a breeze.
I'm telling you. Charles... Charles?
- Charles...
- Hold on. I'm onto something here!
This is pure snow!
It's everywhere! Do you know
the street value of this mountain?
- Charles...
- Wait a minute!
Aahh! Oh!
Outrageous!
I think I froze the left half of my brain!
- Look! I can't move my right arm!
- Get serious.
Look. dude. it's Christmas Eve!
I could be home right now.
drinking this egg-nog
my brother makes with lighter fluid.
You've been staring over that edge
for hours. People die down there!
Dying when you're not really sick
is really sick!
This is very important to me!
If I don't believe in myself. I'm nothing.
I'll be as bad as Ricky Smith.
who snorts nasal spray. I gotta do it!
Nasal spray?
Do you know where I can score some?
- Are you gonna help me?
- All right!
I'll tell you what to do.
Go that way... really fast.
If something gets in your way. turn.
What a coach.
All right. I'm gonna do it.
Whaa-aa-aa...
Uh! Aah!
All right! Now turn!
(MUSIC: "WINTER WONDERLAND")
Hello. Beth. Hey. it's Christmas.
I was thinking
maybe me and you could...
No. we didn't open our presents yet.
You did?
The cutest thing ever?
From Roy.
A giant teddy bear bigger than you?
Sounds great.
No. it really does sound good.
I gotta go.
The Christmas tree's on fire.
# Later on we'll conspire
# As we dream by the fire
# To face unafraid
the plans that we made
# Walkin' in a winter wonderland... #
(BLEEPING)
Open this one next.
I remembered how much you liked
the chocolate nut brownie.
Look. corn and seasoned sauce.
He likes corn.
Ricky. don't be shy.
Give her your present.
Come on. give her your present.
(MUSIC: "HERE COMES
SANTA CLAUS")
- Merci.
- That's a Christmas present.
You have Christmas in France?
Christmas! Christ... mas!
Yeah. it's from Ricky.
You can take that wherever you go
to always remember your trip
to the United States.
How come you're so small?
Now... everyone's going to be wearing
one of these this year.
What have you done?
It's real aardvark fur.
Honey. it's sure... warm.
Now for the best part.
The hood!
- Everybody's going to be wearing one?
- Isn't it fun?
# We'll have lots of fun
with mister snowman
# Until the other kiddies
knock him down!
# When it snows. ain't it thrillin'... #
- What is it?
- I'll show you soon. Almost there.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
- OK? Ta-ra!
- All right.
Al. you've fixed the windows!
Oh. it's a Christmas miracle!
Wait a minute. Mr Bear.
this is crazy! I bet we get her back.
Merry Christmas.
(TINNY MUSIC
LEAKS FROM HEADPHONES)
(BELL)
Hi. Badger. Your book on how to pick
up trashy women came today.
Tell me. what's a little boy like you
doing with big-boy smut like this?
Hi. Lane. I know that
we don't even know each other.
I know you were going out with Beth.
You're not going out with her
any more.
Perhaps I could just be with her.
go to the movies...
Lane. can I talk to you for a moment?
- Yeah.
- Come in and sit down. please.
- Sorry about the garage.
- Let me give you the bottom line.
It would be beneficial if you would
re-enter the sociological mainstream
by dating members
of the opposite sex.
I want to date Beth.
You are going to start dating
other girls. starting tonight.
At six o'clock.
pick up Joanne Greenwald.
- Your law partner's daughter?
- Yes.
- With the big antenna on her face?
- Come on. Lane!
Mellow off. It's a brand-new year.
There's a New Year's Eve dance
at school. You love this disco thing.
- Disco? Come on. Dad!
- You are really... bringing me over!
Six o'clock.
- Right off.
- On.
All right. Joanne Greenwald.
you horrible thing.
Here's your chance
to go out with a stud.
One night with me
and she'll go blind with ecstasy.
I hope she doesn't grab my leg
and start crying when the date's over.
(CAR RATTLES)
All right. Joanne Greenwald.
- (BELL)
- (BARKING)
- Hi. Joanne.
- OK. let's get something straight.
I don't want to go out with you.
This is a favour to my dad.
- I know you're happy to be with me.
- Let's make it easy on ourselves.
We would've had dinner. Ten bucks
apiece. unless you're a cheapskate.
I'll give you
the benefit of the doubt.
We would've ordered double desserts.
That's $22. Tax and tip. $25.
That makes a grand total of $26.37.
half of which
is approximately $13.67.
Now. why don't you just give me
that $13.67 and we'll call it a night?
- You take cheques?
- Sure.
# You never know
if you're the victim of a fool
# I only know
I can't stop thinking 'bout you
# Your love was good
And you take it on the run
# But I fell too hard
And I guess I ain't the one
# Staring the night away
Don't know where you are
# Calling out your name
# This crazy feeling
I'm a one-way love... #
Want a sandwich?
Sure?
You got my vote for cutest couple!
Shave her a little closer
before you kiss her goodnight!
(HYSTERICAL LAUGHTER)
# I've been searching every day
Trying to find another way
# I'd be better off dead
Than to live without you #
(THUNDERCLAP)
# I'd rather be a fool
I'd be lost with someone new
# I'd be better off dead
Than to live without you
# I've been searching every day
Trying to find another way
# I'd be better off dead
Than to live without you
# I'd rather be a fool...#
(CHEERING)
# I'd be better off dead
Than to live without you
# Searching every day
Trying to find another way
# I'd be better off dead
Than to live without you... #
(CAN'T GET WORDS OUT)
(CHEERS AND WHISTLES)
# You're the best thing
That ever happened to me
# I knew right away
I knew right away #
Mon Dieu! Je suis désolée!
It's OK. I was planning on having
my nose flattened by a professional.
Hi. You're that French kid staying
with the dork-heads. the Smiths.
We're neighbours.
- Me. Lane.
- Monique Junet.
- You do speak English?
- Monique!
No? That's OK. I don't speak French.
Monique. I had no idea
where you'd gotten off to.
You shouldn't make me worry.
- Lane...
- Ricky?
You've made Monique's... acquaintance.
Yes. She's a delightful girl
with a firm grip.
Mother will pick us up
at the entrance.
She'll be disappointed if we aren't
at the entrance of the school.
Ricky. you wait
in the front of the school.
When Mom gets here. honk the horn.
Monique and I will continue
our conversation.
You should not upset Mother... ever!
I guess people
do a lot of hand-shaking in France!
Myer! I want to let you know there's
an opening on the water ballet team.
I can make a call if you want.
(MOCKING LAUGHTER)
Monique! Why aren't you with Ricky?
Monique!
Well. nice meeting you.
Goodnight. Parlez-vous?
- Why weren't you there?
- I told her. Mom.
- Don't you understand English?
- Bye!
Two dollars!
(CREEPY MUSIC)
Key!
- Hi. Lane. How was your date?
- They're after me!
(MUSIC AND CHATTER)
(SUDDEN SILENCE)
Happy New Year.
(MUSIC AND CHATTER RESUME)
- Where's Lane?
- He just came in.
He went skiing with Charles De Mar.
I think he's in the shower.
# In me you see a man alone... #
What's taking him? Lane!
I got him this job.
I don't want him to be late.
# A man who listens
to the trembling of the trees
# With sentimental ease
# In me you see a man alone
# Behind the wall
he's learned to call his own
# A man who still goes
walking in the rain... #
Lane? You better...
Myer...
- So you're Al Myer's kid?
- Yes. I am.
- You look pretty stupid to me.
- Thank you.
Let's see if you have any brains.
- You take the meat. Understand?
- Yeah.
- Pat it into pate ball.
- Push it into pate ball.
No. this is a push.
This is a pat.
Take the pate ball
and put it on the tray.
Put on this hat.
You see that sign out there?
You wear it with pride. Put it on!
Ow!
You gotta have pride and class
in this business. You understand?
- What's that?
- Those are the keys.
I want you here
6 a.m. Saturday morning.
This place has to be swept
before the breakfast crew get here.
Roger.
- Where you going?
- To wash my hands.
- Wash your hands on your own time!
- Yes. sir.
- Fat pig!
- What?
Pat pig.
Everybody wants some!
I'll show you what everybody wants!
(THUNDERCLAP)
Mad! Mad! Me. a fool!
(MANIC LAUGH)
It's alive!
# Oh. yeah!
# You can't get romantic
on a subway line
# Conductor don't like it
Says you're wasting your time
# But everybody wants some
# I want some too
# Everybody wants some
Baby. how about you?
# I took a mobile light
looking for a moonbeam
# Yeah. you stand in line
You got lost in a jet-stream
# But everybody wants some
I want some too #
Myer!
(CLANG)
Oops.
Buenos días!
(SNORTS LIKE A PIG)
Looking really good today. buddy.
Looking real good.
Goon.
All right!
This is it!
Whaaa...
Whoa...! Ah!
(TV) Look. a falling star!
Make a wish! If you wish
on a falling star. it will come true...
- What did you wish?
- I can't tell you.
Lane. I know this is awkward.
me being a cartoon and all.
I was just wondering
how you'd feel if I took out Beth.
- Matches...
- Lane. where have you been?
We've all been waiting for you.
Come and sit right down here.
- Have you met Monique?
- Hi.
In honour of our special guest.
I've created Dinner "Mon Doux".
First. we have... Franch fries!
And... Franch dressing!
And... Franch bread!
And to drink... Peru!
You really do go to the outer limits
to make an impression!
Monique. enjoying your stay
in our town?
Are you enjoying your stay
- She doesn't speak English.
- Course she does.
- Are you enjoying your stay?
- She don't speak a word.
I thought these students
had to speak some English!
As we're discovering in our house.
you don't need words to speak
the "international" language.
- Right. Ricky?
- Uh?
The "international" language!
You know!
Love. the language of love!
Monique and Ricky have a regular
cross-continental romance brewing.
Him? And her? That makes sense.
Pardonne-moi.
Où sont les toilettes?
- What's that mean?
- S'il-vous-plaît?
I think she wants
to use the bathroom.
It's down the hall.
second door... on the left. Monique.
Jennifer. this is fabulous liqueur.
Reminds me of the moonshine
Ricky's dead papa used to make.
- God bless him!
- Mrs Smith. no. wait!
I'm sorry your mom blew up. Ricky.
Doctor said she'd be OK.
I guess she just won't be able
to eat any spicy foods for a while.
Oh. no. Not now.
- What do they want?
- A race.
- Lane Myer. the kid from Greendale.
- Here's a good example.
Two brothers. One speaks no English.
The other learned English
from watching sports.
Which is better? Speaking no English
or speaking Howard Cosell?
The chances seem slim
that this once great has the nerve.
the desire to win.
You must obey the speed limits.
A car is not a toy.
- We're tanking. guys!
- Myer takes the lead.
- This could go on Myer's right.
- Lane Myer. slow down!
Lane Myer takes the lead!
It's close. very. very close!
Oh. my God! Ricky's dead!
Ricky. are you dead?
I think he's dead.
Monique. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't...
(SHE LAUGHS)
I'm telling my mom.
(CLANKING)
See you later.
Ever since I got my licence.
they've been after me.
If I had my Camaro running.
I would blow those boys off the street!
(PIG NOISES)
Looks good. huh?
After my mom's cooking.
you'll be able to tolerate anything.
There they are!
My mom means well.
Cooking's her new thing.
She cooks all the time.
It's a lot better than it used to be.
Buenos días!
Bonjour. Voulez-vous couchez
avec moi ce soir?
I'm gonna be picking a new captain
for the ski team on Sunday.
All you gotta do to be captain.
Myer. is beat me.
The try-outs won't be the same
if you're not there... champ.
So. are you and Myer talking about
what a great lover he is?
She only speaks French. Roy.
She doesn't speak imbecile.
Myer. there's one language that
I speak that all women understand.
Just ask your last girlfriend.
Would you like to learn
some new words?
- Shit! Stupid!
- Pardonne-moi! Je suis stupide!
- What's going on?
- Nothing!
Myer's frog girlfriend
is as much of a clod as he is!
You think you're such a tough guy!
I could out-ski you any day!
- Really?
- You want a race. I'll take you on.
- Sure.
- From the K-12. champ!
Chicken!
- What did you say?
- Any time. you name it.
- You're digging your own grave.
- No one has to know.
- Just me and you.
- Sunday. high noon.
You're on.
(PA) This just in!
Lane Myer will be racing Roy Stalin
down K- 12 this Sunday at 12 noon.
(CHEERS AND WHISTLES)
I must be brain-damaged.
I'm gonna race. lose and die.
Est-ce que la voiture ne marche pas?
- That?
- La voiture.
The Camaro? I was telling you
about it. It doesn't work. Nothing works.
My brother's building a space shuttle
out of household appliances.
That'll work.
I can't get that out the drive.
I'll talk to you later. I gotta go.
Smitty! Yo. Smitty!
How's it going?
Here's the ski you called about.
You're all mangled!
Did you get hit by a truck?
No. I was trying to ski the K-12.
After the Olympics. it looked easy.
You gotta be a moron to try to ski
that run. You know what I mean?
- Yeah. Charge it.
- Have a nice day.
This is as bad as it will ever get.
(THUMPING)
I want my two dollars!
Two dollars! I want my two dollars!
No! I can't swim!
No!
Hi. Monique.
Something wrong. Monique?
Nice talking to you.
Yes. something is wrong!
This - how you say - dork-head
is an unleashed sex fiend!
Ricky will not leave me alone!
He thinks I am his love goddess.
his prostrate. Non! Prostitute.
Holy shit! You big faker!
You speak English!
But of course I speak English.
I speak very good English.
I will not speak Mrs Smith's -
qu'est-ce qu'elle dit? -
..."international language of love"
with this reptilian son.
- Mon Dieu!
- Well. honk my hooter!
I don't believe it.
You've understood everything?
If you were with a family like that.
the less you spoke.
the happier you would be.
I never thought of that.
I thought if Casanova and I
had nothing to say. he'd go away.
Instead. he uses it as a chance
to put his testicles all over me!
- His what?
- How you say? Octopus? Testicles?
Tentacles. N. T. tentacles.
- Tentacles.
- There's a difference.
All I want is to come to the States
and see Dodgers' Stadium.
Now all I see is that... that face
in my door every time I move.
The Dodgers. huh?
You have a pretty good pitching arm.
What else is there of interest
in this state but the Dodgers?
I don't know.
You might find a nice friend.
You do have friends in France?
You know. friend! Friend!
- You will not tell?
- That you're a Dodgers fan?
- That I speak English!
- Cross my heart and hope to die.
- Do you?
- Not at the moment.
Monique! Do you know what time it is?
Get in before you catch your death!
Jesus!
You are my friend.
- Goodnight.
- Good luck.
Is that Myer boy bothering you?
Little Ricky's been looking all over
for you! We've been worried sick!
(SHATTERING GLASS)
(DOGS BARKING)
(RADIO: "LIKE TO KNOW YOU WELL")
- Hello?
- Bonjour!
- Hi.
- Comment allez-vous?
No. I already had breakfast.
What are you doing to my car?
What are you doing to my Camaro?
My car is already screwed up
as it is!
- Screwed up. eh?
- Yeah. very.
You got my car running!
- You brought it back from the dead!
- From the dead? Not entirely.
Wait. can you put that back in?
I mean. together. where it goes?
I am sure you will do it.
I fear tools. I made a birdhouse.
The Housing Committee condemned it.
- I can't...
- I cannot do it is your middle name!
- Help me push this into the garage.
- OK.
# People wanna talk about the future
Don't wanna linger on the past
# Just wanna reach the real you inside
# Forget cold glances and rejection
Leave the things that separate
# Build on a trust that we can stand on
# Like to get to know you well
Like to get to know you well
So we can be one
# We can be one together
# Like to get to know you well
Like to get to know you well
So we can be one
# We can be one together
# Like to get to know you well
Like to get to know you well
So we can be one
# We can be one together... #
I think you're kind of remarkable.
How did you learn to do all this?
Some things are not that hard
to understand. Like you. for instance.
You think about ways
of killing yourself but never do it.
- Why is this?
- Isn't that kind of personal?
But I have told you all the details
of my sex life with Ricky Smith!
I figured you could explain
this dramatic death wish.
I used to go out with this girl
named Beth.
I thought I loved her.
She dumped me. I guess I just thought
I couldn't live without her.
You would die to get the attention
of... this woman?
You know. there are better ways
of getting attention.
She dumped me for this real slimebag.
a guy named Stalin.
Stalin! Stalin!
I race Stalin tomorrow! Oh. my God!
- I have to get to a cave!
- This is what I speak of!
This is good way
of getting this attention. Beat him!
Beat him? I can't beat him! I can't!
All you need is a small taste
of success. You will find it suits you.
(ENGINE STARTS)
# Yeah!
# Now. when I was a young boy
# At the age of five
# My mother said I was gonna be
# The greatest man alive
# But now I'm a man
# Way past twenty-one
# Want you to believe me. baby
- # I have lots of fun
- (SHRIEKS)
# I'm a man
# I spell "mmm"
# "Aaa". child
# "Nnn"
# That represents man
# No "B"
# "O" child.
# "Y"
That means mannish boy
# I'm a man
# I'm a full grown man
# I'm a natural-born lovers' man
# I'm a man
# I'm a rollin' stone #
# What is this strange relation
taking life
# Innocent
# To an unknown destination
# And suddenly
# I don't know where I am
# But like a tremor or a spark
# Something's happening in my heart #
One minute.
# I've been arrested by you
Take me in... #
Voilà!
# Finally captured by you
By you. by you
# Take me in
# I've been arrested by you
Take me in... #
Momento.
I got these for Christmas.
Bon appétit.
I wanted to thank you for everything.
Merci buckets.
I forgot the most important thing!
Look at this! How am I supposed
to live through this?
All you do is go that way. really fast.
If something gets in your way. turn!
Watch! It's no sweat!
Now you!
Hell. if you can do it...
Aa-aargh...!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ah! Aah...!
Lane!
Lane. are you all right?
You're mad about me.
No. I'm OK. really. Nothing's broken.
It's just a little... Thank you.
# I can see things in you
# I think I believe in
# And you know I can feel love happen
# And I can make it shine
# 'Cause the light
'Cause the light it shines in you
'Cause the light it shines in you #
(LAUGHING)
Sorry about that.
I'm telling you. Lane.
practically everybody in Northern
California is around this mountain.
waiting to see one Lane Myer
tackle this totally untamed slope.
dead or alive!
So get the lead out. That is all.
- I guess this is it.
- Please hurry.
We have unfinished business.
Do not forget.
- Huh?
- Language lessons.
- You're gonna teach me French?
- The international language.
Kick his ass.
Shit!
I want my two dollars!
Oh. my God!
Two dollars!
I want my two dollars!
The guy chickened out.
He's just a geek.
- Listen. he ain't gonna show up!
- Course not. Shall we pack it up?
No. I might as well
break one more record.
- We'll set the synchros for you.
- OK. we're ready to send Roy down.
- Myer's not going to show.
- Count me down!
- Myer. you don't know when to quit!
- Myer's on the hill!
- Two dollars!
- Go!
Go!
He's skiing on one ski!
Two dollars!
- There's something following them!
- What?!
Two dollars!
I want my two dollars!
- I want my two dollars!
- Not now!
Get lost! Get out of here!
Take a hike. brat!
Aa-aah...!
Two dollars...
They're coming out of the woods!
Come on. little buckaroo! Come on!
(DISTANT CHEERING)
You fiend! You're the hottest thing
since sunburn!
- Nice try.
- Get lost.
Lane. you really are the best!
We've been worried. Monique.
What are you doing? Do you know how
long a drive it is? We're going home.
Excuse me!
This is a sublime metamorphosis
of the Lane Myer
the crowds were expecting to see
at Brodie Mountain today.
Perhaps you can tell us
what brought on
such an enchanting.
exhilarating feat.
Language lessons!
Language lessons.
Inspired words from a man
who knows how to ski.
You little French tramp!
I don't know what Ricky sees in you!
What are you doing with her?
- She's coming with me.
- With us!
You would be wise
to do as Mother says.
Ricky. do something to him!
Son of a bitch!
Come on. nail the sucker!
What are you doing to him?
Come on! That's the boy!
Ha!
Come on!
- Aa-aah...!
- Ya-aah...!
Oh...!
Au revoir!
(SHE GRUNTS)
# With one look
You made me like you. girl... #
Ricky! Ricky. where are you going?
Ricky! Ricky!
# Eyes like starlight
# Through the darkness
you came in sight
# When I was frightened
Looking for something
# I could not find
# You trust and you believe in me
# Believe in me
# Sometimes in a while
Best dreams become reality
# With one look
# All your patience
and sweet persuasion
# You never lied
# When I was hiding
Hiding from something
# I never tried
# Now everything
I used to feel's a memory #
(IGNITION - EXPLOSION)
# Sometimes in a while
Best dreams become reality
# With one look
# You trust and you believe in me
Believe in me
# Sometimes in a while
best dreams become reality
# With one look
# You read me like a book
# Well. I find
You helped me find the strength inside
# All your patience
and sweet persuasion
# You never lied
# When I was hiding
Hiding from something
# I never tried
# Now everything
I used to feel's a memory
# Sometimes in a while
Best dreams become reality
# With one look
# You read me like a book
# I was dying
Just in time you changed my mind
# Eyes like starlight...
# You came in time
# When I was frightened
Looking for something
# I could not find
# You trust and you believe in me
Believe in me
# Sometimes in a while
Best dreams become reality
# With one look
# Eyes like starlight...
# You came but I was blind
# When I was frightened
Looking for something
# I could not find
# Eyes like starlight #